<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Paulus</title>
    <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ben Paulus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Developed a core content strategy for product documentation</title>
      <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/core-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/core-strategy/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge As a newly minted Content Strategy team, we needed a shared vision of our purpose, and the purpose of the Information Development department at McAfee. What was it, exactly, that our department did? What principles could we, as content developers, use to guide our decisions? We needed a core content strategy statement!
The Response It took us three hour-long remote sessions to craft our core content strategy mission statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Established best practices documentation process</title>
      <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/best-practices/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge At McAfee, best practices were spread throughout our product documentation, blog posts, technical articles, and marketing content. Our stakeholders wanted a single location where internal and external customers could find the latest best practices.
In addition, because our product documentation authors were embedded in our development teams, our product documentation had great access to information on new features, but did a poor job speaking to the realities of customer&amp;rsquo;s complex environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implemented top tasks</title>
      <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/top-tasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/top-tasks/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge One of the challenges content authors face is knowing what tasks and content resonate with our customers. For our McAfee ePolicy Orchestrator (McAfee ePO) content, we wanted to find out what information was most valuable to our customers. We already had the usual infrormation about our website: page-views, bounce-rates, time-on-page, but we wanted to know if that information accurately reflected our customer&amp;rsquo;s needs and wants, and if there were any content gaps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measured installation content quality</title>
      <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/content-audits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/content-audits/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge As part of the cross-departmental effort to improve the customer installation experience, we had to make sure the installation content we published to docs.mcafee.com was good content, and that any content changes improved the overall quality of our content.
The Response Taking a page from Kristina Halvorson and Melissa Rach&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Content Strategy for the Web,&amp;rdquo; we determined the quality areas we wanted to measure for our content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redesigned content pages</title>
      <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/content-page-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/project/content-page-redesign/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge Docs.mcafee.com content helps end-users deploy and use their security products, and shortens the time-to-value for McAfee software purchases.
We provide screenshots as part of that content. However, the maximum size of those screenshots was constrained by the layout of our web article pages.
We needed more room for graphics in our web pages. While we were at it, we could also make minor changes to increase the usability of those articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.benjaminpaulus.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a content strategist and information architect looking to lead a distributed content team or help an organization implement a comprehensive content strategy. I believe in empowering employees and end users, and that every touchpoint is an opportunity for dialog, connection, and exchange. I approach content from a customer-focused and evidence driven methodology, leveraging design thinking to solve thorny content challenges, delight customers, and increase end-user autonomy. Specialties Content strategy and analysis, process development, customer jpourney mapping, UX ersearch, team-building, improving communications, writing, editing, indexing and taxonomy, content management systems and migrations, project management, software development processes (including Lean, Kanban, Agile and Scrum), DITA, XML, Git, Markdown, XMetaL, Acrolinx, Tridion Docs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>